===== Поездочки web site =====

----------- Development Tools -----------
1. MS Visual Studio Community 2019
2. Visual Studio Code
3. Angular stuff https://angular.io/guide/setup-local
4. Any MS SQL management tools (those from MS Visual Studio will be enough)

----------- Folders -----------
trips-client
  Root folder for Angular app - client side. This is also root folder for VS Code.
TripsServer
  Directory with MS Visual Studio solution for server app.

----------- Setup Development Environment -----------
Note that VS Code doesn't support spaces in path to the root directory of project,
so make sure the root is mapped to some destination without spaces in path.

1. Create two local MS SQL databases:
a. "Trips" database - for logical data storage, this will contain all the data
  you can enter manually, so it's not expected to take much HDD space.
//---------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------b. "Pics" database - picture data storage, this DB will contain all the pictures
----------  you "upload" to the app, and will therefore grow rapidly.
[!] 2020-05-31: We are currently about to migrate to AWS S3, so everything that is related
to PicsDB and storing pictures in the project will change in few days.
//---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Both databases should use Windows authentication.
You can change this setting, however, in that case you will have to amend not only
configuration files, but the app code as well. In such case, this guide will not help you.
It's for you to choose: to follow these instructions, or to setup everything on your own.

Create both databases as standalone databases (*.mdf files).

2. In TripsServer/Trips/dbconfig.xml change the following parameters:
UseRemote: false
LocalServerName: to whatever is your local MS SQL Server service name (you can take it
  from your DB's connection strings)
LocalTripsPath: full path to *.mdf file of your local "Trips" DB.
LocalPicsPath: full path to *.mdf file of your local "Pics" DB.

3. In TripsServer/Trips/Program.cs:
Uncomment the line "Config.Keys.CreateExample();", then launch the app in debug mode,
make this line execute, then stop the app, and comment the line back.
You will get "keys.example.xml" file in the TripsServer/Trips folder. Rename it to "keys.xml"
and specify there whatever keys you want, or leave default.

4. Create tables in databases. Execute the following lines in NuGet Package Manager Console:
update-database -context Trips.Entities.TripsContext
update-database -context Trips.Entities.Pics.PicsContext

Win7 note: if you don't have certain Win7 updates installed, NuGet will fail to execute these
commands with no description what the error was about. To fix this you must update PowerShell.
Google how to do this.

5. Launch server app in Debug mode. You can use "/ping" endpoint to check that DB connections work well.

6. In trips-client/src/app/services/api.ts:
Change the predefined API path to the address your server app started on.
Then start the Angular app ("ng serve" or trips-client/run.bat).
If the Angular app for some reason started not on the localhost:4200, you should stop the server app
and change ClientUrl value in Program.cs (sorry, didn't make it via config), then rerun server app.

7. On running client app, go to login (upper right corner) and try to log in with username "bn"
and empty password. The app responds "Пользователь bn не найден" (User bn not found) - it's ok.
Now try to login as bn again and use the AppDefaultUserPassword value from TripsServer/Trips/keys.xml
as password.

8. You're in! Congratulations. Start to add data.